The untold true story.
Togo is a adventure, family film directed by Ericson Core.
The untold true story set in the winter of 1925 that takes you across the treacherous terrain of the Alaskan tundra for an exhilarating and
uplifting adventure that will test the strength, courage and determination of one man, Leonhard Seppala, and his lead sled dog, Togo.
Leonhard Seppala, played by Willem Dafoe.
Constance Seppala, played by Julianne Nicholson.
George Maynard, played by Christopher Heyerdahl.
Dr. Curtis Welch, played by Richard Dormer.
Bill Clark, played by Adrien Dorval.
Sally Burdett, played by Madeline Wickins.
Togo is a 2019 American historical adventure film directed by
Ericson Core and produced by Walt Disney Pictures.
The film centers on Leonhard Seppala and his titular sled dog in the 1925 serum run to Nome to transport
diphtheria antitoxin serum through harsh conditions during an epidemic of diphtheria.
The film stars Willem Dafoe,  Julianne Nicholson, Christopher Heyerdahl, Michael Gaston, Michael
McElhatton, Jamie McShane, Michael Greyeyes, Thorbjørn Harr, Shaun Benson, and Nikolai Nikolaeff.
It was released on Disney+ on December 20, 2019.
The movie received generally positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of snowstorm, husky,
based on true story, puppy, alaska.
The tone is uplifting.